—— 真 爱 字 幕 组 ——
招贤纳士QQ群：319832261
新浪微博：@幸福ing形式
后期：幸福ing形式
翻译  校对：幸福ing形式
我感觉到阳光拂面
I feel the sun on my face.
我看到了绿树环身
I see trees all around me,
野花在微风中吐露芬芳
scent of wildflowers on a breeze.
如此怡人
It's so beautiful.
在这一刻  我并不是身陷太空
In this moment, I'm not stranded in space.
距地球上的人类遭核难灭顶事件
It's been 97 years since a nuclear apocalypse
已经97年了
killed everyone on Earth,
只留下辐射在那个星球暗流涌动
leaving the planet simmering in radiation.
幸运的是  还有幸存者
Fortunately, there were survivors.
在爆炸发生那一刻
12 nations had operational space stations
12个国家运行着太空站
at the time of the bombs.
如今只剩方舟号了
There is now only The Ark,
由众多太空站锻造而成
one station forged from the many.
我们被告知地球还需100年
We're told the Earth needs another 100 years
才能适宜人类居住
to become survivable again.
困于太空四代之久
4 more space-locked generations,
人类才能回家  回到地球
and man can go home, back to the ground.
地球  梦之所向  这就是事实
The ground, that's the dream. This is reality.
319号囚徒  面朝墙
Prisoner 319, face the wall.
现实烂透了
Reality sucks.
这是干嘛？
What is this?
安静  伸出右臂
Quiet. Hold out your right arm.
不  不是  我时候还没到
No. No. It's not my time.
再有一个月我才18
I don't turn 18 for another month.
伸出你右臂
Hold out your arm.
在方舟号上  任何罪名
On The Ark, every crime,
无论大小  均被判以死刑
no matter how small, is punishable by death
- 除非你未满18岁  - 你的表
- unless you're under 18. - Your watch.
不  这是我爸爸的
No. It was my father's.
- 取下来  - 不
- Take it off. - No.
不
No.
少年犯均被关在此处…看管
Juvenile offenders get put here... lockup.
我们叫它天箱
We call it the sky box.
319号囚徒
Prisoner 319...
Clarke  站住  在这儿等着
Clarke, stop. Wait here.
妈妈？妈妈  发生什么了？
Mom? Mom, what's going on?
这怎么回事儿？
What is this?
快点  走
Come on. Let's go.
他们要杀了我们  是吗
They're killing us all, aren't they,
他们要为剩下的人活着
reducing population to make more time
缩减人口吗？
for the rest of you?
Clarke  你不是在被处决
Clarke, you are not being executed.
你要被送往地球
You're being sent to the ground,
你们100个人
all 100 of you.
什么？但这并不安全
What? But it's not safe.
不不
No. No.
我们18岁时会被复审
We get reviewed at 18.
条律变更了
The rules have changed.
这给了你活下来的机会
This gives you a chance to live.
你会优先照料他人
Your instincts will tell you
这是你的本能使然
to take care of everybody else first,
如同你的父亲  但是一切小心
just like your father, but be careful.
我不能连你也失去
I can't lose you, too.
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
地球  Clarke
Earth, Clarke.
你要去地球了
You get to go to Earth.
地球百子 第一季第一集
—— 真 爱 字 幕 组 ——
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
听着
Look.
Wells  你为什么在这儿？
Wells, why the hell are you here?
当我发现他们在送囚犯
When I found out they were sending prisoners
去地球  我就故意被他们抓了
to the ground, I got myself arrested.
为你而来
I came for you.
那是什么？
What was that?
是大气层
That was the atmosphere.
方舟号的囚徒们  听好了
Prisoners of The Ark, here me now.
你们被给予再次机会
You've been given a second chance,
身为你们的长官
and as your Chancellor,
我希望你们明白
it is my hope that you see this
这个机会不仅是你们的
as not just a chance for you,
也是我们的
but a chance for all of us,
是人类众生的
indeed for mankind itself.
我们对你们降落地境遇一无所知
We have no idea what is waiting for you down there.
如果幸存率较高
If the odds of survival were better,
我们会派送其他人
we would've sent others.
坦白说  之所以送你们去
Frankly, we're sending you because
是因为犯罪使你们毫无价值
your crimes have made you expendable.
Wells  你爸真混蛋
Your dad is a dick, Wells.
你们的罪行会被赦免
Those crimes will be forgiven,
记录会被清除
your records wiped clean.
20分钟前我看到一架飞船被发射
I saw a ship launch not more than 20 minutes ago.
谁在里边？
Who was on it?
是囚禁者吗？他们还只是孩子
Was it the prisoners? They're just kids.
他们是去地球了吗？
Are they going to Earth?
有什么变动吗？
Has something changed?
各位  如我所说  此时
Folks, as I said, at this time,
我们无法证实或否认任何事
we cannot confirm or deny anything.
拜托  女士
Come on, lady!
我儿子在那架飞船上
My son is on that ship.
降落点经过精挑细选
The drop site has been chosen carefully.
最后次大战前  韦瑟山
Before the last war, Mount Weather
曾是建于高山里的军事基地
was a military base built within a mountain.
库存了足量的不易腐坏物资
It was to be stocked with enough non-perishables
可供300人两年使用
to sustain 300 people for up to two years.
太空漫步强势回归
Spacewalk bandit strikes again.
继续啊  Finn！
Go, Finn!
瞧瞧
Check it out.
你老爸最终还是让我漂浮了
Your dad floated me, after all.
迫降伞打开前你应该坐好了
You should strap in before the parachutes deploy.
嘿  你俩  想活命就别解开
Hey, you two, stay put if you want to live.
韦瑟山就是生命之源
Mount Weather is life.
你们必须马上找到这些物资
You must locate those supplies immediately.
你就是那个
you're the traitor
被监禁一年的背叛者？
who's been in solitary for a year.
而你就是那个因为非法太空漫步
You're the idiot who wasted a month of oxygen
而浪费一个月氧气的白痴
on an illegal spacewalk.
但那很有趣
But it was fun.
我叫Finn
I'm Finn.
你们的职责之一是活下去
Your one responsibility is stay alive.
呆你座位上
Stay in your seats.
Finn  你还好吗？
Finn, are you ok?
先别说
Not now.
我们看到的就是
Total system failure,
系统完全失效
that's what we're looking at.
我们所知道的是当我们失去联系
All we know for sure is that they were off course
他们偏离了航道  所以…
when we lost contact, so...
那通讯网络呢
Tell me about communications.
除了他们手腕上的遥感装置
Other than the telemetry from their wristbands,
其他一无所获…没有音频  没有视频
we got nothing... no audio, no video,
也没电脑链接
no computer link.
所有为协助他们而植入的程序
Everything that we programmed in
都失效了
to help them is gone.
他们只能靠自己了
They're on their own.
推进器现在也该打开了
Retrorockets ought to have fired by now.
这飞船上的所有东西
Ok. Everything on this ship
都有百年寿命了吧
is 100 years old, right?
让飞船飞一会儿
Just give it a second.
Clarke  我必须得告诉你
Clarke, there's something I have to tell you.
我很抱歉害你父亲被捕
I'm sorry I got your father arrested.
你别和我谈我父亲
Don't you talk about my father.
求你了  我不能在临死前
Please, I can't die knowing
还让你恨我
that you hate me.
他们没有逮捕我父亲  Wells
They didn't arrest my father, Wells.
他们处决了他  我也恨实了你
They executed him. I do hate you.
听
Listen.
没机器的轰鸣声了
No machine hum.
哇噢
Whoa.
还是头一次
That's a first.
Finn  他还有呼吸吗？
Finn, is he breathing?
外舱门气压变低了
The outer door is on the lower level.
- 我们走吧  - 不
- Let's go. - No.
我们不能就这样开门
We can't just open the doors.
嘿  就推上闸就行了  伙计们
Hey, just back it up, guys.
别打开
Stop.
空气可能有毒
The air could be toxic.
无论如何  我们都是死
If the air is toxic,
就算空气有毒
we're all dead, anyway.
Bellamy？
Bellamy?
天啊  瞧瞧你长多大了
My God, look how big you are.
你穿的什么鬼东西
What the hell are you wearing,
警卫制服？
a guard's uniform?
靠它我才能进来这飞船
I borrowed it to get on the drop ship.
总得有人来照顾你啊
Someone has got to keep an eye on you.
你的腕带呢？
Where's your wristband?
关你啥事？
Do you mind?
我一年没见我哥哥了
I haven't seen my brother in a year.
我们都没兄弟姐们啊
No one has a brother.
她是Octavia Blake
That's Octavia Blake,
那个被发现藏起来的女孩儿
the girl they found hidden in the floor.
Octavia  Octavia  不要
Octavia, Octavia, no.
我们来做点别的
Let's give them something else
好让他们记住你
to remember you by.
什么？比如？
Yeah? Like what?
比如百年来的踏足地球第一人
Like being the first person on the ground in 100 years.
贱乖乖们  我们回来了！
We're back, bitches!
为什么这样严肃啊  小公主？
Why so serious, princess?
又不是我们在大爆炸中丧命
It's not like we died in a fiery explosion.
你应该对那倆跟随你
Try telling that to the two guys
离开自己座位的人说
who tried to follow you out of their seats.
你不喜欢被叫小公主
You don't like being called princess,
是吗  小公主？
do you, princess?
看到那山峰了吗？
Do you see that peak over there?
嗯哼
Yeah.
韦瑟山
Mount Weather.
要吃饭就得穿过
There's a radiation-soaked forest
中间那片饱经辐射的林地
between us and our next meal.
丫的我们被降错地方了
They dropped us on the wrong damn mountain.
就是那里
There it is.
他们已经着陆了
We know they've landed,
但通讯系统失效
but communications are down,
这意味着我们仍对地球
which means we're still blind
一无所知
to conditions on the ground.
幸好有Abby的腕带
Thanks to Abby's wristbands,
最起码我们还能知道
at least we know how those conditions
他们身体影响变化的信息
affect the human body, which is
比这百年来了解到的多得多
more than we've had for 100 years.
做的好
So nice work.
那么  这些说明了什么？
Now, what are they telling us?
两个孩子死了  已经黑屏了
Two dead kids, dark tiles.
Jackson教授  请你向Kane委员解释下
Dr. Jackson, please share our theory
我们的臆测
with Councilor Kane.
好的
Of course.
Granted  他们仅仅着陆七分钟
Granted, they've only been on the ground for 7 minutes,
但现在  我们认为意外死因是
but as of now, we believe the fatalities
不安全着陆  并非辐射
are due to the landing, not radiation levels.
在我们与飞船失去联系时
Both boys died at the same time
两个男孩同时死去
that we lost contact with the drop ship.
不安全着陆？这就是你们的推测？
Rough landing? That's your theory?
与此相关
The dots connect.
如果是因为辐射  那你是否同意
Would you agree that if it was radiation,
我们很快就会看到死亡人数上升？
we'd see fatalities climb fairly quickly now?
因为我看显示器可是满屏红啊
Because I'm noticing a lot of red on that board.
生命体征数值增加  有两种可能
Spiking vital signs, two possibilities...
其一  着陆时受伤
one, injuries sustained during landing.
其二呢？
And the other?
在那儿他们内心澎湃
They're excited to be there.
我们有麻烦了
We got problems.
通讯系统失灵了
The communications system is dead.
我去了仓顶
I went to the roof.
大量仪表盘丢失
A dozen panels are missing.
高温烧熔电线
Heat fried the wires.
好吧  现在最棘手的是
Well, all that matters right now
前往韦瑟山
is getting to Mount Weather.
明白？看
See? Look.
我们在这儿
This is us.
如果我们想活命
This is where we need to get to
这儿就是我们的目的地
if we want to survive.
你从哪儿学的这些？
Where'd you learn to do that?
你父亲
Your father.
啊  酷  地图啊
Ah, cool, a map.
这片镇子有酒吧吗？
They got a bar in this town?
我请你啤酒
I'll buy you a beer.
说话注意点儿
You mind?
嘿 嘿  嘿
Hey, hey, hey,
拿开你的手  他是我们一伙儿的
hands off of him. He's with us.
放松点儿
Relax.
我们就是试图找到我们在哪儿
We're just trying to figure out where we are.
我们在陆地上
We're on the ground.
这对你来说不够好吗？
That not good enough for you?
我们得找到韦瑟山
We need to find Mount Weather.
你也听到我爸说的了
You heard my father's message.
那才是我们该先做的
That has to be our first priority.
去你的老爹吧
Screw your father.
怎么  你以为这里是你辖区吗
What, you think you're in charge here,
你  还有你的小公主？
you and your little princess?
你以为我们在意是谁管吗？
Do you think we care who's in charge?
我们需要去韦瑟山
We need to get to Mount Weather
不是因为长官那样说
not because the Chancellor said so,
而是因为我们拖得越久
but because the longer we wait,
我们就会越饥肠辘辘
the hungrier we'll get
境况会变得更糟
and the harder this'll be.
如果没有那些补给
How long do you think we'll last
你们觉得我们会撑多久？
without those supplies?
我们去的地方有20英里的路程
We're looking at a 20-mile trek, ok?
所以如果我们想在天黑前到达
So if we want to get there before dark,
我们现在就应动身
we need to leave now.
我有个更好的主意
I got a better idea.
你们俩去  为我们找寻
You two go, find it for us.
换换特权人士来做劳苦工作吧
Let the privileged do the hard work for a change.
耶  对嘛
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
你没听到吗  我们都需要去
You're not listening. We all need to go.
看啊  大伙儿
Look at this, everybody...
地球长官啊
the Chancellor of Earth.
有意思？
Think that's funny?
- 啊！- Wells
- Uh! - Wells.
对  上啊  拿下他
Yeah. Come on. Get him.
不  但也是  来吧
No, but that was. All right.
你还能怎样啊  Wells？
What you gonna do now, Wells?
上啊  来啊
Come on. Come on.
他只有一条腿
Kid's got one leg.
何不等他好了公平决斗呢？
How about you wait until it's a fair fight?
嘿 太空步行者
Hey, spacewalker,
下回也救救我
rescue me next.
怎么？他挺可爱啊
What? He's cute.
他是个犯人
He's a criminal.
他们都是
They're all criminals.
听着小O  我来这里是保护你的
Look, O. I came down here to protect you.
我不需要保护
I don't need protecting.
我被锁禁一生了
I have been locked up one way
一生都是如此
or another all my life.
我不要再言听计从了
I am done following orders.
我得找点乐子  Bell
I need to have fun, Bell.
我得放纵疯狂一下
I need to just do something crazy
就因为我可以  现在
just because I can, and no one,
没人能阻止我  包括你
including you, is gonna stop me.
我不能和他们呆一起  小O
I can't stay with them, O.
你在说些什么啊？
Now what are you talking about?
去找点东西吧
Go find something.
我动了点手脚  好吗
I did something, ok,
为上飞船
to get on the drop ship,
我做了足以使他们一下来
something that they will kill me for
就杀了我的事儿
when they come down.
我现在还不能说是什么
I can't say what it is just yet,
但你得相信我
but you have to trust me.
你还相信我  是吗？
You do still trust me, don't you?
是
Yeah.
那么韦瑟山  什么时候出发？
So Mount Weather. When do we leave?
现在
Right now.
明天我们会带着食物回来
We'll be back tomorrow with food.
可是你俩怎么带回
How are the two of you gonna carry
100人的口粮？
enough food for 100?
是我们四个  现在能走了吗？
4 of us. Can we go now?
听起来不错  加我一个
Sounds like a party. Make it 5.
嘿  你到底在干吗？
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
- 出去走走啊  - 嘿
- Going for a walk. - Hey,
你试图取下这个吗？
were you trying to take this off?
恩  怎么？
Yeah. So?
通过这个腕带
So this wristband transmits
方舟号会收到你的生命体征
your vital signs to The Ark.
取下它  他们就认为你死了
Take it off, and they'll think you're dead.
我该在乎这个吗？
Should I care?
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
只是你想爱你的人
Do you want the people you love
认为你死了吗？
to think you're dead?
你想让他们两月后也下来吗？
Do you want them to follow you down here in two months?
可是如果他们以为你死了
Because they won't
就不会下来了
if they think we're dying.
好了
Ok.
我们走吧
Now let's go.
去吧
Go on.
你不该来的  Wells
You shouldn't have come here, Wells.
不管你怎么想  Finn是我的
Before you get any ideas, Finn is mine.
不管你怎么想  我不在乎
Before you get any ideas, I don't care.
嘿  亲爱的  Clarke怎么样？
Hey, darling, how's Clarke?
生命体征强健
Her vital signs are strong,
血糖偏低
blood sugar is low.
她没进食
She hasn't eaten.
我是Griffin教授
This is Dr. Griffin.
我就来
On my way.
Jackson  放下手里的活儿
Jackson, put it out there
我们需要输血
we need blood...
A型阴性  大量的
"A" Neg. And a lot of it...
然后马上赶往手术室
and then get your ass to the O.R.
Abby  发生什么了？
Abby, what's wrong?
长官被射伤了
The Chancellor has been shot.
瞧  那伙计  才是老手
Now, that, my friend, is game.
那东西  老兄  是毒漆树
That, my friend, is poison sumac.
什么？那是？
What? It is?
花儿没毒
The flowers aren't poisonous.
事实上  花可入药  用以镇定
They're medicinal, calming, actually.
我家在方舟上种了很多药草
His family grows all the pharmaceuticals on The Ark.
伙计们  你们能跟上吗？
Hey, guys, would you try to keep up?
拜托  Clarke  你怎能无视这些啊
Come on, Clarke. How do you block all this out?
额  很简单啊
Well, it's simple.
就想想为什么没见这里有动物
I wonder, "Why haven't we seen any animals?"
也许因为这儿本就没有
Maybe it's because there are none.
也许因为我们已经暴露在
Maybe we've already been exposed
足以要了我们命的辐射里
to enough radiation to kill us.
这儿是很美  但还是跟上吧
Sure is pretty, though. Come on.
真该有人出来给她喂点儿毒漆树
Someone should slip her some poison sumac.
我想知道你俩干啥被抓起来了
I got to know what you two did to get busted.
漆树不是花园里的唯一植物
Sumac is not the only herb in the garden,
如果你懂我的意思
if you know what I mean.
有人拿了后忘记物归原位
Someone forget to replace what we took.
有人道歉也有千次了吧
Someone has apologized, like, 1,000 times.
你呢 Octavia？
How about you, Octavia?
他们抓你是因为？
What'd they get you for?
因为出生了
Being born.
这可不是老手该问的
That is so not game.
还说没动物  啊哈？
No animals, huh?
长官失血过多
Chancellor has lost a lot of blood.
如果及时发现他就好了  该死
If only they found him sooner, damn it.
他醒了
He's waking up.
再来点镇定剂
Increase the anesthesia.
我们用了太多的血浆和镇痛剂
We used way too much blood and anesthesia.
超过标准线了
We're way over the line.
你的长官就要休克了
Your Chancellor is going into shock.
你这是让我触犯法律
You're asking me to break the law.
那好  我自己来
Fine. I'll do it myself.
让他们有事儿找我
Let them come after me.
打扰了  先生
Excuse me, sir.
您说有消息就让来告诉您
You asked to be notified if there was news.
长官仍在手术中
The Chancellor is still in surgery,
但我们已查明射杀者身份
but we have I.D.Ed the shooter.
Bellamy Blake  方舟上
Bellamy Blake is the only person
唯一一个下落不明的人
on The Ark unaccounted for.
他是谁？
Who is he?
不是什么人物  门警而已
He's no one, a janitor.
我们仍在为其做侧写
We're still working up a profile,
但他去地球的动机很明确
but his motive for going to Earth is clear.
他妹妹  我记得
Sister. I remember.
她母亲藏了她16年之久
Her mother kept her hidden for almost 16 years,
几近记录
nearly a record.
怎么了  Shumway指挥官  有话快说
What is it, Commander Shumway. Spit it out.
我们现在就能开始了
We could start now.
在长官手术时
As Chancellor pro tempore,
你可以下达命令
you can give the order
执行人口缩减计划
to start reducing the population.
还不是时候
Not yet.
先生  我们是在浪费时间
Sir, we're wasting time.
缩减百人
Removing the 100 from the population
也仅仅只能换来一月光景
only buys us another month.
工程师需要更多时间修理系统
Engineering needs more than that to fix those systems,
如果它能被修好
if they can fix them at all.
你明白我意思  指挥官  别说了
You have my answer, Commander. Enough.
如果我们得杀害数百无辜民众
If we're gonna kill hundreds of innocent people,
我们就按照条律进行
we're gonna do it by the book.
明白了吗？
Is that clear?
与此同时  我想知道
In the meantime, I want to know who helped
是谁帮助那个门警进入飞船
this janitor get on that drop ship
我确信他一人之力是无法成事的
because he sure as hell didn't do it by himself.
看起来我们之中有叛徒了  指挥官
Seems we have a traitor in our midst, Commander,
而且这百人之中竟存杀手
and the 100 have an assassin in theirs.
找到水了？
Find any water yet?
还没  不过…
No, not yet, but...
如果你也来的话  我再去找点
I'm going back out if you want to come.
你知道的  我父亲
You know, my father,
在气压舱时
he begged for mercy
为不被放逐太空
in the airlock chamber
而向你爸跪地求饶
when your father floated him.
你拼错“Die”（死）了 天才啊
You spelled "Die" Wrong, geniuses.
如果你要杀了某人
If you're gonna kill someone,
最好别先说出来
it's probably best not to announce it.
你不会是真的门警吧  是吗？
You're not really a member of the guard, are you?
不是  不过真的马上就来
No. The real guard will be here soon
除非我们阻止他们
unless we stop it.
你该不会真的认为
You don't actually think
他们会宽恕了你的罪名吧
they're gonna forgive your crimes.
就算他们宽恕了  然后呢？
Even if they do, then what?
像我们这类人
Guys like us,
还能成为模范公民吗？
we're gonna become model citizens now,
找工作  幸运的话
get jobs, if we're lucky,
- 也就拾拾垃圾  - 你什么意思？
- maybe pick up their trash? - You got a point?
没什么  就一个疑问
No. I got a question.
他们把你关起来  放逐你们到这里
They locked you up, dumped you down here
像实验室里的待死白鼠
like lab rats to die.
那你为什么还帮他们呢？
So why are you helping them?
我们傻吧
The hell we are.
你们还带着那些遥感呢  不是吗？
You're wearing those bracelets, aren't you?
现在  这些东西正在告诉他们
Right now, those things are telling them
他们随后下来是否安全
whether or not it's safe to follow us down.
好  你说我们能阻止这  怎么做？
Ok. You said we could stop it. How?
先取下它
Take them off.
神舟号以为你们死了
The Ark will think you're dead,
那么下来就不安全
that it's not safe to follow.
懂吗？
You follow?
对  那我们取下来
Right, and if we do,
我是说  我们有什么好处？
I mean, what's in it for us?
我需要有人帮我管理这里
Someone has got to help me run things.
嗨  Ab  长官怎么样？
Hey, Ab. How's the Chancellor doing?
如果他挺过今晚的话
Ask me again
你再问我吧
if he makes it through the night.
我们又失去谁了？
Who else did we lose?
Murphy和Mbege家的  都叫John
Murphy and Mbege, both named John.
在着陆时都未受伤
Neither was injured during landing.
我同意  其他原因致死的
I concur. Something else killed these two.
上一秒  还好好的
One second, they were fine,
下一秒  就玩完儿了
and the next, bang.
所以不会是辐射
Then it isn't radiation.
拜托   Abby
Come on, Abby.
科学可不是靠痴心妄想
Wishful thinking isn't good science.
这不是痴心妄想
It's not wishful thinking.
上一秒  好好的  下一秒  就死了
One second, fine, the next, bang
这不是被辐射致死的表现
isn't how exposure to radiation presents.
好吧  如果辐射足够强就有可能
Well, it could be if there was enough of it.
如果辐射足够强
If there was enough of it,
他们所有人都会死
they would all be dead.
拜托  让我对吧
Please let me be right.
嘿  知道我一直想知道什么吗？
Hey, you know what I'd like to know?
为什么97年后送我们来这里？
Why send us down today after 97 years?
有什么变数吗？
What changed?
谁管啊？我很高兴他们这样做
Who cares? I'm just glad they did.
我都快在牢房发霉里
I woke up rotting in a cell,
现在呢  我却在树林里遛弯
and now I'm spinning in a forest.
也许他们在卫星里发现了什么
Maybe they found something on a satellite,
你知道的  像旧的气象卫星什么的
you know, like an old weather satellite or...
不是卫星
It wasn't a satellite.
方舟号资源正在枯竭
The Ark is dying.
现在的人口数
At the current population level,
也就撑个3个月
there's roughly 3 months left
现在估计四个月吧
of life support,
因为我们走了
maybe 4 now that we're gone.
所以为此秘密
So that was the secret
他们才把你关起来
they locked you up to keep,
也是为什么单独关押你
why the kept you in solitary,
你父亲被放逐的原因？
floated your old man?
我父亲就是发现此缺陷的工程师
My father was the engineer who discovered the flaw.
他认为人们有权利知道
He thought the people had a right to know.
而委员会反对  我妈妈也是
The council disagreed. My mother disagreed.
他们担心由此会引发惊慌
They were afraid it would cause a panic.
我们就要公诸于众  但这时  Wells…
We were gonna go public, anyway, when Wells...
怎样  告发了你父亲？
What, turned in your dad?
不管怎样  警卫在公布前早到了
Anyway, the guard showed up before we could.
这就是今天局势造就的原因
That's why today.
也是值得以身犯险的原因
That's why it was worth the risk.
即使我们死了  最起码
Even if we all die, at least
他们获得了更多的时间
they bought themselves more time.
他们会杀了更多人  不是吗？
They're gonna kill more people, aren't they?
好吧  他们这般对我
Good. After what they did to me,
我想说  把他们都放逐了吧
I say, float them all.
你不是说真的吧
You don't mean that.
我们得去警告他们
We have to warn them.
我父亲也是这样说的
That's what my father said.
哦  天啊  我爱死地球了
Oh, damn, I love Earth.
哦！ 天啊
Oh! Holy...
Octavia  你到底在干吗？
Octavia, what the hell are you doing?
Octavia…
Octavia...
我不会游泳
I can't swim.
我知道啊  我们可以站着啊  哈哈
I know, but we can stand. Ha ha ha!
等等  这儿不该有河流的
Wait. There's not supposed to be a river here.
可是  这儿就有啊
Well, there is.
所以赶快脱了衣服吧
So take off your damn clothes.
Octavia  快上来
Octavia, get out of the water.
快上来啊！
Get out of the water now!
Octavia！
Octavia!
不
No.
那丫是什么东西？我们得帮她
What the hell is that? We have to help her.
- 我们该怎么做？  - 尽量别被吃了
- What are you gonna do? - Try not to get eaten.
不不  等等
No. Wait.
如果我们分散它注意力
If we distract it,
也许它能放开她  帮我
it might let her go. Help me.
不！
No!
有用了  它放开她了
It worked. It let her go.
你能上来吗？
Can you get to the shore now?
我抓到你了
I got you.
它回来了
It's coming back.
它朝你去了  伙计
It's headed right for you, guys.
拜托  快啊  继续游
Come on. Come on. Keep going.
好了
Ok.
谢谢你  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
你没事了
You're gonna be ok.
我记住了
Note to self...
如有下次  英雄救美
next time, save the girl.
耶  继续啊  宝贝儿
Yeah. Go on, baby.
耶  接着啊
Yeah. Keep going.
下一个是谁？
Who's next?
你们在搞什么？
What the hell are you doing?
释放自我啊
We're liberating ourselves.
不然你以为呢？
What does it look like?
我看你是在把我们全都害死
It looks like you're trying to get us all killed.
通讯系统已经毁了
The communication system is dead.
我们就剩这些腕带了
These wristbands are all we got.
取下它  方舟号就以为我们都死了
Take them off, and The Ark will think we're dying,
他们会认为地球不安全
that it's not safe for them to follow.
正是如此  长官
That's the point, Chancellor.
我们能照顾好自己  对吗？
We can take care of ourselves, can't we?
对！
Yeah!
你认为我们是来玩儿的吗？
You think this is a game?
上边的人不仅仅有我们的亲朋好友
Those aren't just our friends and our parents up there.
还有农民  医生  工程师
They're our farmers, our doctors, our engineers.
我不在乎他给你们说了什么
I don't care what he tells you.
依靠自己  我们无法在这儿生存
We won't survive here on our own...
除此之外  如果这儿真安全
and besides, if it really is safe,
难道你不想让其余的人
how could you not want the rest
也能够下来吗？
of our people to come down?
我的人都下来了
My people already are down.
那些人把我的人关押起来
Those people locked my people up.
那些人为我母亲生了二胎
Those people killed my mother for the crime
而处决了她
of having a second child.
都是你父亲做的
Your father did that.
- 法律又不是我父亲写的  - 对
- My father didn't write the laws. - No.
他只是强制执行它们
He enforced them,
但再也不会了
but not anymore,
这儿不会如此
not here.
在这儿  没有法律
Here, there are no laws.
- 哇噢  耶吼  - 酷
- Yeah. Yeah. - Cool.
在这儿  我们身随心动  为所欲为
Here, we do whatever the hell we want
身随心动  为所欲为
whenever the hell we want.
你不必看惯它  Wells
Now, you don't have to like it, Wells.
看不惯你阻止或改变它啊
You can even try to stop it or change it,
杀了我啊
kill me.
知道吗？
You know why?
你可以身随心动  为所欲为
Whatever the hell we want.
身随心动  为所欲为！
Whatever the hell we want!
whatever the hell we want
身随心动  为所欲为！
身随心动  为所欲为
whatever the hell we want
下雨了！ 真的雨啊！
Rain! Real rain!
看啊！
Check it out!
是水！
It's water!
我们得把它收集起来
We need to collect this.
我说了  身随心动  为所欲为
Whatever the hell you want.
又十个了  一个接一个的
10 more, one after the next.
Abby  快看血浆渗透压
Abby, look at plasma osmolarity.
显示器表明正在上升
It's going up across the board.
他们找到水源了
They found water.
Abigail Griffin委员
Councilor Abigail Griffin,
由于你使用了
you're under arrest
超越医药用品的最大限量
for exceeding the maximum medical supplies allowed
你被逮捕了
for a patient.
抱歉  这需要公之于众
Sorry this has to be public.
关于此事  政策规定相当明确
The policy in these matters is very clear...
没有特殊待遇
no special treatment.
那你到底用了多少血啊  Abby？
How much blood did you use, Abby?
别回答
Don't answer that.
需要多少就用多少
I used whatever it took.
通过违法来阻止你升为长官
Breaking the law to keep you from becoming Chancellor
是我做过的最轻松的决定
was the easiest decision I've ever made.
鉴于此事
In that case,
你如此坦白
given your confession,
身为临时长官
in my role as Chancellor pro tempore,
我只能定你罪行  别无他法
you leave me no choice but to find you guilty.
办法总是人想的  Kane
We always have a choice, Kane.
你选择控告我的丈夫
You chose to press charges against my husband,
你的朋友  即使你知道
your friend, even though you knew
他会被因此放逐
he would get floated for it.
还将我女儿囊括在内
You chose to include my daughter in those charges,
现在你选择如此
and now you're choosing this.
藏在法律背后  躲避一切罪责
Hiding behind the law absolves you of nothing.
就算这样  根据
Be that as it may, in accordance
刑法第一条
with penal code one,
成人犯罪
because all crimes
无论罪责大小
committed by those above the age of maturity
一律死刑
are capital crimes,
由此你将被处以死刑
you are hereby sentenced to death.
明早行刑
Execution is set for the morning,
而我的选择是
and I choose at every turn
不惜一切代价
and at any cost
确保
to make sure
人类依旧存活
that the human race stays alive.
这就是我们的不同之处  Kane
That's the difference between us, Kane.
我是要确保
I choose to make sure
我们是否值得活下去
that we deserve to stay alive.
美呆了  对吗？
Pretty cool, huh?
你去河边了？
Did you go to the river?
我想这还是值得冒下险的
Figured it was worth losing a finger or two.
拿着
Here.
你就抿一小口？
You call that a sip?
你觉得这会不会
You think this means we're all
让我们都张两个脑袋？
gonna grow two heads?
哎呦  美女也是会笑的啊
What do you know? She can laugh.
好了  来看看这个
Come on. You have to see this.
这是个脚印
That's a toe.
另外  据我判断
Plus, near as I can tell,
不管它是什么  都是两只脚走路的
whatever it is, it's walking on two feet.
我猜  是猴子
My Guess... monkeys.
抱歉啦  我只是
I'm sorry. It's just,
据我所知
according to everything I've read,
这附近并没有两足动物的
there were no bipedal animals anywhere near here,
绝对不会是猴子
certainly not monkeys.
好吧  那你知不知道
Right. You read anything about
森林深处有什么
glow-in-the-dark forests
或者食人蛇？
or man-eating snakes?
你疯了吧
Are you out of your mind?
你不能随意杀害
You can't just kill everyone
任何反对你的人
who disagrees with you.
现在  你也以为我是坏人了
Now, you all think I'm a bad guy,
可是只有我才能为人类存活
but I'm the only one who's willing to do
而愿倾尽一切
what it takes to save us.
她可是我最好的朋友
She's my best friend.
那你想让我说什么
So what do you want me to say,
说对不起？
I'm sorry?
我不会
I'm not.
友情对我们来说奢侈难负
Friendship is a luxury we can't afford,
就算将要变成只有亚当夏娃的宇宙
and if I have to take us down to a cosmic Adam and Eve
我也会如此的
I will do it.
拜托  仁慈点儿吧
Please, show mercy,
就算不为Abby  为我想想吧
if not for Abby, then for me.
仁慈也是负担
We can't afford mercy, either.
走得够远的了
That's far enough.
我不想射杀你  Wells
I don't want to shoot you, Wells...
见鬼  我倒挺喜欢你
hell, I like you...
但我也确实需要他们
but I do need them
认为你死了
to think that you're dead.
为什么？说真的  为什么这样做
Why? Why are you doing this, for real,
别说那些我说什么
not some crap about getting to do
你做什么的废话
what you want to do?
我有我的原因  枪也在我手里
I have my reasons. I also have the gun.
所以我来问
So I ask the questions,
我说
and the question is,
为什么你不帮我？
why aren't you helping me?
你老爸驱逐了你  Wells
You dad banished you, Wells, and yet
而你在这儿  仍为他做事
here you are, still doing his bidding,
遵守规则
following the rules.
难道你还没有厌烦
Aren't you tired of always doing
一直被派遣吗？
what's expected of you?
反抗他吧
Stand up to him.
取掉腕带  你会惊讶于
Take off that wristband, and you'll be amazed
那种自在感觉的
at how good it feels.
不
No.
绝不  想都别想
Never. Not gonna happen.
还不清楚吗？
Is that clear enough for you?
好  知道了
Yeah. It is.
抱歉得这样
I'm sorry it had to be this way.
不  不  放开我！不！
No! No! Get off of me! No!
拿下他  快撂倒他
Get him down. Put him down.
不！拜托  伙计  放我走
No! Come on, man. Let me go.
行了  快动手
Get it. Do it.
不！不要这样！  别这样！不  不
No! Don't do this! Don't do this! No. No!
不要啊！
Come on, man. Aah!
Griffin教授  时间到了
Dr. Griffin, it's time.
Callie
Callie.
够了
That's enough.
替我照看好Clarke
Watch out for Clarke for me.
好
Ok.
Jackson  好好利用腕带
Jackson, use the wristbands.
可能会有方法逆转设计
There may be a way to reverse-engineer them
进行通讯
for communication.
和Sinclair谈谈设计
Talk to Sinclair in engineering.
明白就点头
Nod if you understand.
住手
Stop.
Griffin教授被赦免了
Dr. Griffin is pardoned.
等会儿再处理你
I'll deal with you later.
开门
Open the door.
我说  开门
我花了12个小时把那些内脏缝合
I spent 12 hours putting those intestines back together.
现在带他躺回床上
Get him back to bed now.
给我说说那地球百子
Tell me about the 100.
他们成功了吗？
Did they make it?
是你想打头阵的  别磨蹭了
You wanted to go first. Now quit stalling.
韦瑟山还等着呢
Mount weather awaits.
就荡到极点处
Just hang on till the apogee,
你会成功的
and you'll be fine.
那会像个印第安人  是吧？
The apogee like the Indians, right?
极点而已  又不是阿帕奇族（发音相似）
Apogee, not apache.
他知道的  快吧  Finn
He knows. Today, Finn.
恩  恩  队长  那边见
Aye, aye, captain. See you on the other side.
- 等等  - 怎么？
- Wait. - What?
让我来
Let me.
我可以的
I can do it.
就知道你内心还有小宇宙
Knew there was a badass in there somewhere.
嘿  害怕没什么的  Jasper
Hey, it's ok to be afraid, Jasper.
窍门就是战胜它
The trick is not fighting it.
那边见了  啊哈！
See you on the other side. Ha ha!
呜 呼！耶！
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Yeah!
我们就是极点！
We are apogee!
耶！
Yeah!
哈  呼！
Yes! Whoo!
做得好！
Yeah! Whoo!
你成功了  Jasper！
You did it, Jasper!
呼哈！耶
Whoo! Yeah!
我们也去吧  小公主
Let's go, princess.
你先
You're up.
快点  Clarke！你也能的！
Come on, Clarke! You got this!
呜呼！  极点啊！
Whoo! Apogee!
我们做到了！
We did it!
韦瑟山！
Mount weather! Whoo! Whoo!
帅！
Yes!
做得好  Jasper！
Yeah, Jasper!
Jasper
Jasper.
拜托  拜托  挺住  Jasper！
Come on. Come on. Come on. Jasper!
Jasper！  不  不要
Jasper! No. Come on.
趴下  趴下
Get down. Get down.
快
Come on.
这儿还有别人
We're not alone.
—— 真 爱 字 幕 组 ——
招贤纳士QQ群：319832261
新浪微博：@幸福ing形式